muttropolis.com 2008-05-09

# Privacy & Security: Muttropolis.com

**Privacy Policy**

At Muttropolis, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, which is why we do not sell, rent, or loan any personal identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. We hope the policy below will answer all of your questions regarding how we treat information gathered from visitors to Muttropolis. Feel free to email us at [bark@muttropolis.com](mailto:bark@muttropolis.com) with any questions you might have.

**What Information We Collect**

In order to process your order efficiently, we collect the following information: name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number ("Personal Information") when you place an order with us. This information is used solely by Muttropolis and is stored in a secure environment. Under certain circumstances we do also collect the user's IP address, but only when we suspect that credit card fraud may have occurred. We also periodically conduct surveys of visitors to our Web site. This helps us better understand what our customers would like to see from us. We use this information for internal marketing research purposes. We may contact a visitor who responded to a survey for more information, but only if that visitor has told us that they don't mind being contacted.

**Use of Information that You Provide**

At Muttropolis we collect Personal Information only for the purposes of fulfilling orders, providing a high level of customer service, gaining knowledge internally regarding what our customers want and mailing circulars and special offers from Muttropolis. We do not give or sell Personal Information to any other party. If at any time you do not want to receive offers and/or circulars from us, you can always remove yourself from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to [bark@muttropolis.com](mailto:bark@muttropolis.com). 

**Opt-out Email policy**

We ask that you tell us when you do not wish to receive periodic emails from us. We will only send email for customer service purposes and to those visitors who have indicated that they wish to receive other types of email from us. If at any time you wish to stop receiving email from us at any time, you can always remove your name from our mailing list by sending an email to [bark@muttropolis.com](mailto:bark@muttropolis.com) stating that you wish to unsubscribe. 

**Security of the Information You Provide**

Among our top priorities is keeping your Personal Information secure. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which provides the highest level of security currently available for secure transactions, to encrypt all of your Personal Information before it is transmitted to us. Encrypted information cannot be read or recorded as it travels over the Internet. You can tell you are sending information securely by the unbroken key icon or closed lock icon that should appear at the bottom of your internet browser's window (depending on what browser you use). These icons will appear when you are placing an order on our Web site. In addition, you will see our site address change slightly, from http: to https: indicating a secure server connection is being used. Additionally, access to your Personal Information is provided only to our employees and agents who have a need to know such information for the purpose of fulfilling your order and offering our high level of customer service. The computers that store your Personal Information are located in a separate facility which employs the latest in firewall and security technology. 

**Use of Cookies**

We use cookies to provide our customers with streamlined ordering and other useful features. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies make Web surfing easier for you by saving your customer identification information while you're at our site. The use of cookies has become an industry standard used by most major Web sites. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Please continue to review our privacy policy from time to time so that you are aware of our current policy with respect to cookies. 

**Your Acceptance of these Terms**

By using our Web site, you agree to accept the Muttropolis privacy policy. Make sure you read this policy carefully, because if you do choose to use our Web site, you automatically agree to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Web site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove these terms.
